

## **Professional Summary**

I am a highly motivated and skilled software developer with five years of professional experience and a record of spearheading the development of important software projects. I would like to grow in to a technical leadership role.

## Education

### University of Ottawa, Ottawa, Ontario

Master of Science - Mathematics

Fall 2015 - Summer 2017

Thesis The Convex Hull of the Highest Weight Orbit and the Carathéodory Orbitope

## Carleton University, Ottawa

BSc - Mathematics and Computer Science

Fall 2010 - January 2015

11.92/12 GPA

Honours Project Torsion Points on Elliptic Curves

### Technical Skills

#### Languages and technical skills:

- Algorithmic trading: working with market data and trading systems
- Strong Python skills
- Strong C/C++ skills multithreading and optimizing for performance
- Strong debugging skills (gdb, valgrind)
- · Solid foundations in computer science

#### Dev-ops and automation:

- Containers: Docker and Kubernetes
- Jenkins
- Apache Airflow
- Make and CMake

#### Other skills:

- Startup experience
- Flex and Bison
- The LLVM framework
- Embedded development: some experience with NXP IMX and Raspberry Pi pico
- Some experience with X86 and ARM assembly language

# Experience

## SociVolta Senior Software Developer

November 2019 - April 2023

Montreal, QC

- Worked closely with research team to develop trading tools
- Responsible for development and maintenance of key trading tools, including an interpreter for a domain specific language which we used to express our trading strategies using Python and Pandas
- Responsible for important automation ground work: automated jobs for pulling market data and executing transactions using Apache Airflow and Python
- Maintenance of Jenkins jobs for the company's services
- Mentoring junior members

### ZeligSoft

January 2018 - November 2019

Software Developer

Gatineau, QC

- Development and maintenance code generation tool for OpenSplice DDS: Tool written in C which translated OMG IDL into language-specific stubs
- Development and maintenance of JavaScript bindings for OpenSplice DDS
- Maintenance of Python bindings for OpenSplice DDS
- Maintenance of OpenSplice build system (CMake, Jenkins)